[
  {
    "question": "Nom",
    "response": "Schupp",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 147.61061946902655,
      "y": 690.625
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Prénom",
    "response": "Guillaume",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 320.7079646017699,
      "y": 690.625
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Date de nais.",
    "response": "08/01/2004",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 475.75221238938053,
      "y": 692.75
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Adresse complète",
    "response": "Rue Neuve 28 Hannut",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 123.1858407079646,
      "y": 683.1875
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Unité Guide (Région, n°, nom)",
    "response": "Cacahuette",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 161.41592920353983,
      "y": 670.4375
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 1 Nom",
    "response": "Fabrice",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 86.01769911504425,
      "y": 610.9375
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 1 : Lien de parenté",
    "response": "Oncle",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 118.93805309734513,
      "y": 601.375
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 1 : Période du",
    "response": "07/03/2005",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 98.76106194690266,
      "y": 590.75
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 1 : au",
    "response": "07/03/2027",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 142.30088495575222,
      "y": 589.6875
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 1 : tél",
    "response": "02 558 85 85",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 77.52212389380531,
      "y": 569.5
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 1 GSM",
    "response": "0478 87 89 90",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 81.76991150442478,
      "y": 561.0
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 1 E-mail",
    "response": "fabrice@gmail.com",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 89.20353982300885,
      "y": 550.375
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 1 Remarque(s)",
    "response": "Parent sympa",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 109.38053097345133,
      "y": 542.9375
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 2 Nom",
    "response": "Isabelle",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 336.63716814159295,
      "y": 608.8125
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 2 : Lien de parenté",
    "response": "Mamie",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 370.6194690265487,
      "y": 601.375
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 2 : Période du",
    "response": "01/09/2024",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 349.3805309734513,
      "y": 591.8125
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 2 : au",
    "response": "31/08/2025",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 393.98230088495575,
      "y": 591.8125
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 2 : tél",
    "response": "02 987 65 43",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 329.20353982300884,
      "y": 572.6875
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 2 : GSM",
    "response": "0499 87 65 43",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 330.2654867256637,
      "y": 559.9375
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 2 : E-mail",
    "response": "isabelle@email.be",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 336.63716814159295,
      "y": 551.4375
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Parent 2 : Remarque(s)",
    "response": "belle mamie",
    "position": {
      "page": 1,
      "x": 360.0,
      "y": 541.875
    }
  }
]